affiliatetheme.net 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy - Affiliate Theme 3.0 Affiliate Theme 3.0 - Affiliate Theme 3.0

AffiliateTheme.net Privacy Policy  
Last Revised August 1, 2014

Introduction  
We’re AffiliateTheme. We revolutionized the affiliate theme site building business with Word Press templates and user friendly software in 2009. Let us explain how we protect your privacy and give you our privacy policy.

Lots of Word Press affiliate marketing related websites seem like they’re just providing the information you want as a pretext to get your personal information for solicitation or marketing purposes. Our site is designed to be widely accessible without requiring you, our users, to provide your personal information. Still, some really useful features that we want to provide are naturally going to require some identifying or personal information to make them work well. But fear not, this policy is here to help you understand what we do with the information we collect on this site.

About This Policy  
AffiliateTheme (“Affiliate Theme net ” or “AT” “we”, “us”, etc.), through the AffiliateTheme.net Web site, related data, and/or related services (collectively, the “Services”), collects information about its users that may be personally identifiable. In that understanding, we have adopted this privacy policy, which we will comply with when we gather and use information from users of the Services. This is our current policy as of its last revision date at the top, but please note that we may make changes or additions to our privacy policy from time to time, so before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy, you should check the Services for the most current version.

Collection of Information  
AffiliateTheme collects a variety of information relating to usage of the Services.

Information You Provide  
You may provide us information about yourself, such as providing your name and contact information. We use this information to respond to your requests, and to provide and improve the Services. We may combine this information with other information we collect from the Services or from other companies.

Cookies  
Cookies are bits of electronic information that can be transferred to a user’s computer to uniquely identify the user’s browser. When you visit the Services, we place one or more cookies on your computer. The use of cookies helps us improve the quality of the Services in various ways, such as identifying which Services are most interesting to you, or storing information you may want to retrieve on a regular basis or tracking user trends. You may adjust settings on your browser to refuse cookies. Some Services and features may not function property if you disable cookies.

Usage Logs  
When you access the Services, your computer communicates a variety of information to computer servers operating the Services, including the existence of cookies, your Internet Protocol address, and information about your browser program. These may be used to roughly determine your physical location or Internet provider in order to analyze website usage and to provide relevant content and/or advertising. Your usage also creates a record of what information you are requesting from the Services.

Usage and Disclosure  
Generally, AffiliateTheme.net uses the information collected to provide the Services and to communicate with you.

We will only share personal information in the following circumstances:

Consent  
When you consent or direct AffiliateTheme.net to share the information.

Affiliates and Service Providers  
When AffiliateTheme.net provides personal information to our affiliated companies or service providers to manage and use on our behalf, consistent with the terms of this privacy policy.

Aggregation  
We may share with third parties aggregate information or information that does not personally identify individuals.

Legal Obligation or Protection from Harm  
When AffiliateTheme.net has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the personal information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any requirement of law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce or investigate a potential violation of the Terms of Use, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise respond to fraud, security or technical concerns, or (d) protect the rights, property, or safety of AffiliateTheme, its users, or the public against harm.

Merger, Sale or Liquidation  
When and if AffiliateTheme.net is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its business, personal information may be transferred along with the business.

Third Party Web Sites  
The Services may include links to the Web sites of other companies and/or individuals. These third party Web sites may collect personal information about users, and AffiliateTheme’s privacy policy does not extend to these external Web sites and third parties. Please refer directly to these third parties and Web sites regarding their privacy policies.

Children Under the Age of 13  
We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13. The Services are not designed to attract the attention of persons under the age of 13.

Storage and Security of Information  
Personal information will be processed and stored by AffiliateTheme.net in databases hosted in the United States. AffiliateTheme.net has taken reasonable steps to protect the information users share with us, including, but not limited to, setup of processes, equipment and software to avoid unauthorized access or disclosure of this information.

Contacting Affiliate Theme  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the privacy practices of the Services, please contact us by e-mailing wally@AffiliateTheme.net.

Thanks  
Wow, thanks for making it down to the end. Seriously, though, if you have any suggestions about this policy, or if anything was unclear, raised your eyebrows, or seemed dubious, please contact us at privacypolicy@AffiliateTheme.net with your thoughts.
